Lynn Hershman-Leeson Papers M1452
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 4: Administrative Files, 4
  - Siemens 1993 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence 1993 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Festivals 1993 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - The Art Gallery 1993 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Bills 1993 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Poland 1993 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - IFP 1993 (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Double Click Face 1993 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - University of California 1993 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Research 1993 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Double Click Face Correspondence 1993 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Releases 1993 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Double Click Face 1993 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence 1993 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Video Positive 1993 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Art Center 1993 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - POV 1993 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - ISEA 1993 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Misc 1993 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Rijksmuseum 1993 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - BAVC 1993 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence 1993 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - London 1993 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Resumes 1993 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Sales 1993 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Misc 1993 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Poland 1993 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Digital Village 1993 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Galleries 1993 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Maryland 1993 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - SF State 1993 (Box 106, Folder 8)
- Series 5: Exhibitions, Screenings, Film Festivals, and Lectures, 5
  - Subseries 5.01: Exhibitions, 5.01
    - High Tech/Low Tech Hybrids March 26 - June 16, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - I-5 Resurfacing April 2001 - April 2002 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Gallery 16 Editions 2001 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Das Zweite Gesicht May 8 - August 11, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Parallels and Intersections June 1 - November 3, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Obsession July 13 - August 31, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Bay Area Conceptualism June 1 - September 1, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - e.space August 17 - November 24, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Lynn Hershman - New Work September 4 - 28, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - PhotoGENEsis: Opus 2 November 9, 2002 - February 9, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - New York Digital Salon January 2003 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Die Wohltat der Kunst September 14 - November 10, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Genomic Issue(s): Art & Science February 25 - April 5, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Dutch Electronic Art Festival February 25 - March 9, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - 10th NY Digital Salon April 22 - 23, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Vertigo Screening Benefit June 21, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Bitforms Preview Show June 26 - July 28, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Writing Identity: Autobiography in Art June 22 - August 27, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Only Skin Deep December 12, 2003 - Feb 29, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - 100 Artists Interpret the Tzedakah Box November 14, 1999 - January 23, 2000 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Ich ist etwas Anderes Feb 19, 2000 - June 18, 2000 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Verbindingen Jonctions 4 May 6 - 27, 2000 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - net_condition Sept 23, 1999 - Feb 27, 2000 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Art Entertainment Network / Let's Entertain Feb 12, 2000 - Nov 25, 2001 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Meaning and Message Nov 6, 1999 - March 12, 2000 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Inter Media_City Seoul 2000 Sept 2, 2000 - Oct 31, 2000 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Cross Female Sept 30, 2000 - Oct 29, 2000 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Tempus Fugit: Time Flies Oct 15 - Dec 31, 2000 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Made in California 1900 - 2000 Oct 22, 2000 - Feb 25, 2001 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Prix Arts Electronica 99 September 6, 1999 (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - Connected Cities: Processes of Art in Urban Network June - August, 1999 (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 5.02: Screenings, 5.02
    - Nashville Independent Film Festival June 5 - 9, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Toronto International Film Festival September 6 - 14, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - The Hamptons International Film Fest October 16 - 20, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Film Festival October 24 - 27, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - San Francisco Int'l Film Festival April 18 - May 2, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - "New Film Works" April 18, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Taos Talking Picture Festival April 11 - 14, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Seattle International Film Festival May 23 - June 16, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Women with Vision: Restless Age March 1 - 23, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Sundance Film Festival January 10 - 20, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Seventh Art June 13, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Mondavi Center January 27, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Video I: I for Independent April 2003 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Conceiving Ada (Theatrical Opening) June 2003 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Warsaw Film Festival November 3 - 14, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Berlin Int'l Film Festival February 6 - 16, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - 21st Brussels Int'l Fest of Fantasy Film March 14 - 29, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - 30 Jahre Internationales Forum de Jungen Films Retrospective 2000 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - TV Dinner @ The Kitchen Feb 5 & 6, 2000 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Sundance Channel April 2000 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Trading Images Sept 22 & 29, 2000 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Feminale Film Festival September 24-26, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Cinemayence Film Festival November 2-3, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 5.03: Film Festivals, 5.03
    - San Francisco Film Festival: SF Int'l Film Festival Program Guide April 18-May 2, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - San Francisco Film Festival: SF Int'l Film Fest Mini Guide April 18-May 2, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - San Francisco Film Festival: A Feast of a Festival Jeffrey Anderson March 27, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - San Francisco Film Festival: Views, Reviews, Previews Janos Gereben April 17, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - San Francisco Film Festival: Festival Features Films from.... Sura Wood April 2002 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - San Francisco Film Festival: SF Film Festival Opens This Month Sura Wood April 11, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - San Francisco Film Festival: SF Film Festival to Open with.... Carla Meyer March 27, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - San Francisco Film Festival: S.F. Festival Offers.... Mary Pols April 18, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - San Francisco Film Festival: The Grande Dame of Festivals Jeanne Aufmuth April 19, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - San Francisco Film Festival: A World of Movies Robert Sokol April 18, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - San Francisco Film Festival: Menlo-raised Producer's Film.... Pam Smith April 24, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - San Francisco Film Festival: Airing More than Just Laundry.... Kathlee Wilkinson April 24, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 27)
    - San Francisco Film Festival: Film Festival comes to Park Theatre The Almanac April 24, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 28)
    - San Francisco Film Festival: Something for Everyone at SF.... Marco Cerritos April 22, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 29)
    - San Francisco Film Festival: Crouching Actor, Hidden Talents Ruth Stein April 26, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 30)
    - San Francisco Film Festival: Crouching Actor, Hidden Talents Ruth Stein May 8, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - San Francisco Film Festival: Local Talent Shines at 45th SFFF Allen White April 2002 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - San Francisco Film Festival: Features - Festivals: Teknolust Rod Armstrong May 1, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - San Francisco Film Festival: The Grande Dame of Festivals Jeanne Aufmuth April 27, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - San Francisco Film Festival: Neo, New, Nuevo B. Ruby Rich April 17-23, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco Film Festival: United Nations Karen Silver April 17-23, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - San Francisco Film Festival: Lynn Hershman Leeson Nancy Cooper Frank November 2002 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - San Francisco Film Festival: Worlds of Fantasy and Fact Robert Harrison December 2002 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Letters to answer (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Gaze (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Arthur Freyer: correspondence (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Follow up on (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Film Fest/Letters: pictures (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Film Fest/Letters: correspondences (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Film Fest/Letters: "San Francisco International Film Festival" (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Film Fest/Letters: "Running From the Light" draft (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Film Fest/Letters: correspondences (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Media (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - ZKM: London Art (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - ZKM (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 5.04: Lectures, 5.04
    - "Vision: Filmmakers in Conversation" March 25, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - "Picture Talk Quarterly" March 2002 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - IFFCON: Funding the Digital Future 2000 (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - Arts Council of Napa Valley 2000 (Box 97, Folder 19)
    - Symposium on Issues in Net Art 2000 (Box 97, Folder 20)
    - College Art Association Conference 2000 January 14, 2000 (Box 97, Folder 21)
    - Sins of Change Symposium February 16 and 19, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Kala Art Institute February 23-26, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Where Media Collide Speakers Series 2000 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Work of Art in the Age of Digital Technology April 6-8, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - UC DiMI-DIGIVATIONS Conference April 8, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - The Kitchen and GroundZero Conference May 3, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Interactivity and Digital Cinema May 19, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Columbia College Fall Lectures and Workshops November 11-12, 1999 (Box 106, Folder 17)
    - Mixed Media November 2, 1999 (Box 106, Folder 18)
    - Technology in the 1990s April 12, 1999 (Box 106, Folder 19)
- Series 6: Reviews and Publicity, 6
  - Series 6.01: Reviews 1974-1986, 6.01
    - Chronological File: March 1986 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Reviews 1973 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Reviews 1975 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Reviews 1976 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Reviews 1977 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Reviews 1978 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Reviews 1981 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Reviews 1982 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Reviews 1983 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Reviews 1984 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Reviews 1985 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Reviews 1986 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Miscallaneous Correspondence & Reviews (1981-1985) (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Drawing Research (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Miscallaneous Documents (1 of 2) (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Miscallaneous Documents (2 of 2) (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Reviews & Research 1981 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Work & Reviews 1981 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - San Francisco State University Student Evaluations 1987 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Miscallaneous Reviews & Correspondence 1977 & 1982 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Robert Janz & Fred Conway 1976 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Review Index by Year (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Albright, Thomas "A Ghostly Hotel Room Tableau"- San Francisco Chronicle December 22, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Albright, Thomas- San Francisco Chronicle: August 31, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Alexander, Terry "Fan at Mills College"- Artweek: January 14, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Allman, Paul "Recognizing Art as Entertainment"- Berkeley Gazette: September 1, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Allman, Paul "The Bad & The Beautiful"- Berkeley Gazette: August 1, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Miscallaneous Announcements (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Atkins, Robert " Space Age Art From BART to Bow & Arrow"- San Francisco Bay Guardian: August 3, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Atkins, Robert " Space Age Art From BART to Bow & Arrow"- San Francisco Bay Guardian: August 3, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Atkins, Robert "State of the Arts in San Francisco: Not Bad" (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Ballatore, Sandy "Lynn Hershman as Roberta Breitmore"- New Performance Magazine; Vol. I, Issue 2 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Battcock, Gregory "Art in America"-Domos; Vol. 566: January 1976 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Battcock, Gregory "Why Art?" (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Battcock, Gregory "New York Exhibition; the Hypocritical Ill- 3 Artists in New York"-Domus Vol. 566:January 1976 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Battcock, Gregory "New Artists Video" (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Gregory Battcock "Cocktails at Bonwit's"- SoHo Weekly News: November 4 1976 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Battcock, Gregory "Cocktails at Chez Bernar"- SoHo Weekly News: April 26, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Blum, Walter "Museum Without Walls"- California Living: April 3, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Bourdon -Art in America: July-August 1977 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - City- Ten Top Exhibits (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Bundock, Cindy- "New Class Examines Media Myths"- September 17, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Burnham, Jack "San Quentin Mural Project"- The New Art Examiner; Vol 4, No. 8: May 1977 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Chipman, Jack "Interview with Lynn Hershman"- Artweek: July 1, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Coddington, Lew "Prison Mural, a Window to the World" (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Coffelt, Beth "The End of the Game"-Sam West Eulogy- California Living: May 18, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Conen, Ronny H. "Lynn Hershman at Annina Nosel"- Artforum; Vol. 19, No. 9: May 1981 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Bourbon, David "Folies Legeres at Bonwit's"- Village Voice; Vol. XXIV: November 8, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Dunham, Judith "Painting the Walls of San Quentin"- Artweek: September 4, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Frankenstein, Alfred "The Macabre Rooms of the Wax Ladies"- San Francisco Chronicle: October 13, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Frankenstein, Alfred "Artist Should Stick to her Trade" (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Alfred Frankenstein "The Floating Museum Murals"- San Francisco Chronicle: July 22, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Frankenstein, Alfred "Collage; Lynn Hershman: Bedtime Story"-Art News; Vol. 74: February 1975 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Frankenstein, Alfred "A Space Invasion in our Midst"- San Francisco Chronicle: July 13, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Miscallaneous Articles & Reviews (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Glueck, Grace "Art People"- The New York Times: October 22, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Regina Hacket "Woman's Many Faces"- Artweek: November 29, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Harris, Robert "On the Optical Rotation of Linearly Polarized Light Beams"- Journal of Chemical Physics; Vol. 65, No. 12 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Heiss, Alana "Interview with Lynn Hershman"- Currant Magazine Vol. 5: September 1976 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Keller, Marti "Mackeral Stretched Thin"- The Berkeley Independent Gazette: October 28, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Kuhn, Annette "Culture Shock: April Fool" (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Larkin, Kathy "Bustin at Bonwit's" or "Window Stopping"- New York Daily News: October 9, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Loeffler, Carl "Lynn Hershman"- Art Contemporary; Vol. 2, No. 1:Summer 1976 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Loeffler, Carl- Art Contemporary; Vol. 1, No. 4: September 1976 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Lyons, Harriet "Store Windows: All Dressed Up and Going Way Out"- Ms.; Vol. 5, No. 5:November 1976 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - McCann, Cecile "Lynn Hershman"- Artweek: September 19, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - McDonald, Robert "The Art of Display"- Book Review (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Miscallaneous Reviews (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Minton, James "Trespassing at the Dante"- Artweek: Decemner 22, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Perreault, John "Masked Marvels"- SoHo Weekly News: October 27, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Ratcliff, Carter "Report from San Francisco" Art in America: May-June 1977 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Ratcliff, Carter "The American Artist: From Loner to Lobbyist"- Art in America; Vol. 65: February-March 1977 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Restany, Pierre "New York 1977"-D'Ars (Milano): April-May 1977 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Rosler, Martha "The Private & the Public Feminist Art in California"- Art Forum; Vol. 16: September 1977 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Roth, Moira "An Interview with Lynn Hershman"-LAICA Journal; Vol. 17: January-February 1978 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Roth, Moira "Toward a History of California Performance: Part One"-ARTS: February 1978 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Roth, Moira "(H)errata" a conversation about (h)errrata with Lynn Hershman & Jo Hanson with Moira Roth: Ocotber 18, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Ross, Janice "Global Performance"-Artweek: August 26, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Roth Interview (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Schlessinger, Norma "Art on Review"- Sausalito Review: August 1978 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - "American Narrative/Story Art 1967-77" (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Art In America: May-June 1977 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Selz, Peter "Lynn Hershman at the Dante Hotel"- Art in America; Vol. 62: March 1974 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Selz, Peter "6 Artists in Search of a Definition"- Ar News; Vol. 72, No. 8:Summer 1973 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Pertraitis, Louise- Video Art Display in Floating Museum (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Simpson, Blaise "Interview with Lynn Hershman" (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Art In America: March-April 1974 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Subseries 6.02: Publicity, 6.02
    - Miscellaneous material: gallery and museum showings, photos, etc. 1963-1973 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Art and Artists: New Directions 4: Palomar College, San Marcos, CA, Spring: Announcement, audio tapes 1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - ArtVenture, AREA, New York, NY: Announcement (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Art Forum: magazine March, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - The Bulletin of the Cleveland Museum of Art, 45th May Show; includes Catalog, Lynn Lester (Hershman) p. 105; various announcments. 1963 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Business Cards: New York, 1974; Myth America, no date (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Completed Fragments, University Art museum, UC-Berkeley: Announcement Nov. 8-26, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Centro Attivita Visive, Palazzo de Diamante, Ferrera, Italy: Announcement cards 1978 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - A Collection of New Art for Jimmy Carter, Georgia Museum of Art, University of Georgia-Athens, January, 1977[?] (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - The Diaries of Guglielmo Achille Cavellini, 1975, Johannes Gutenberg, ed.: Booklet (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Eight Young Artists, Los Angeles Art Association, November [?]: Announcement (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Feingarten Galleries, Los Angeles, CA, September [?], Hershman exhibition announcement: Announcement (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Five Women Artists in Las Vegas, University of Nevada Las Vegas Gallery, March 3-14, 1975: exhibition announcement (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - The Graphics Gallery, San Francisco, CA, Sept 1-22, 1970: postcard exhibition announcement. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Ice and Air Videotape [Lake George] (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Insights, San Francisco Museum of Art: stationary (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Installations, Hotel Project, Oakland, CA, July 3 - Aug. 16 [?] (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - International Art Festival, Westwood Art Association, Century City Los Angeles, CA, Nov. 1-13, 1965: exhibit catalog (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Jody Scully Gallery, Los Angeles, CA, Apr. 14 May 9, 1973: Announcement (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Mackeral: Set design for Berkeley Stage Company production; includes Rough sketch of set design, reviews, photos. Oct. 24, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Mark Rennie interview (transcript) no date (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Restructuring the Public Image of Jerry Rubin (ts, photocopies) Oct 31, 1975 - June 1, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Mills College Art Gallery: Announcement 26691 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - New Ways of Consciousness, Inc.: Photocopies of articles of incorporation 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Reflex (The Red Shoes) 1986 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Richmond Art Center, CA, Women's Women exhibit: Poster Sep 20 - Oct 21, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - San Francisco Museum of Art, List of Classes: Brochure Spring, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - de Saisset Art Gallery and Museum, University of Santa Clara, CA: Announcements July 5-30, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - San Francisco Video Review at Video Free America, San Francisco, CA: Poster schedule no date (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Santa Barbara Museum of Art, CA: Post card announcement May 3 - June 5, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Smith-Anderson Gallery Invitations: Post card announcement Feb 28 - Mar 27, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Son of X-Ray Man, William Sawyer Gallery, San Francisco, CA: announcements Sep 1 -19, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Stationary - misc. no date (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Surrounding Areas, Civic Arts Gallery, Walnut Creek, CA: Catalog Dec. 3 - Jan. 11, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Third Dulin National Print and Drawing Competition: Catalog May 10 - June 18, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Touch, Feel, and Play, Civic Arts Gallery, Walnut Creek, CA: Catalog no date (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Traditions and Alternatives of the Art and Artists, Palomar College, San Marcos, CA: College calendar/mailer March, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Untitled Group Show, Mills College Art Gallery, Oakland, CA; inlcudes Announcement, interdepartmental correspondence. Jan. 7 - 28, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Valerie Hudson Dance Theater; includes Correspondence, grant application, miscellaneous brochures, announcements. 1981-1986 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Lethal Recognition; includes Grant application, correspondence. 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Women in Performance Art: Announcement, photocopy 1981[?] (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Women U.S.A., Laguna Beach Museum of Art, CA; includes Brochure of entrants and Juror's award winners. no date (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Visiting Faculty Exhibit, Worth Ryder Art Gallery, UC-Berkeley, CA: Announcement no date (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - The Year of the Women, The Bronx Museum of the Arts, NY; includes Catalog, annnouncement card. Jan 16 - Feb 20, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Visual Dialog: The Quarterly Magazine of the Visual Arts, vol 3 no 2 (Hershman mentioned on p 27) Winter, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Early Public Relations (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Lady Luck, Las Vegas, NV; includes photos, itinerary, correspondence, brochure, miscellaneous material March, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Scrapbook contents; includes photos, correspondence, announcements, miscellaneous material. 1972 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Scrapbook contents; includes correspondence, grant application, photocopied reviews, etc. 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Reviews, announcements, etc. (Photocopies) mid-1980s (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Venice Bienalle; includes correspondence, press releases, insurance documents, miscellaneous material. 1986 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Ross, Dorien. "Conflict Between Autonomy and Affiliation in the Woman Artist: A Case Study Approach," dissertation, The California School of Professional Psychology at Berkeley (Photocopies) no date (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Subseries 6.03: Publications, 6.03
    - CTRL [SPACE]: Internationaler/Medien/Kunstspreis 2001 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Newfangle 2001: Fort Mason, October 25, 2001 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - "Private I, Private Eye, 2001": CTRL [SPACE] (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - "Transgenic Cyborg"; Eikon: Internationale Zeitschrift Fur Photographie Und (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 6.04: Press, 6.04
    - Misc. Articles 2000-01 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - The SF Chronicle "Virtually Real Sets for the New Movie" p.D-1 8/15/1996 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - The SF Bay Guardian; Conceiving Ada. August 7-13,1996 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - SF Weekly; Ups and Downs, page 33 April 12-18,1995 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Art Week; SAM, Paranoid Mirror November 1995 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Bay Times; Virtual Love, page 41 September 23, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - domus: Architecture Design Art Communication June 1999 (Box 65, Folder 14)